[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why does Peter get beaten up by a bar owner in the movie Forgetting Sarah Marshall?", "correct_answer": "He took a picture off the wall in the restroom.", "incorrect_answers": ["He threw a glass at the bar owner.", "He tried to pick up one of the girls that worked at the bar", "He puked all over the bar owner."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Friday the 13th, when Annie is trying to get to Camp Crystal Lake she stops at a small cafe to ask for direction. How far do they tell her the lake is from there?", "correct_answer": "20 miles", "incorrect_answers": ["15 miles", "25 miles", "10 miles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Jean Roberts in the Billy Jack movies?", "correct_answer": "Delores Taylor", "incorrect_answers": ["Delores Del Rio", "Barbara Eden", "Elizabeth Montgomery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Doctor Dolittle is the central character of a series of childrens books by this author.", "correct_answer": "Hugh Lofting", "incorrect_answers": ["J. K. Rowling", "Lewis Carroll", "L. Frank Baum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You are doing a handwriting analysis test. You choose green ink. What does this say about you?", "correct_answer": "You are adaptable and desire harmony.", "incorrect_answers": ["You are very friendly and spiritual.", "You have a desire to stand out from the crowd.", "You enjoy leadership and dominance."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the bread called Flatkaka appear for the first time?", "correct_answer": "Iceland", "incorrect_answers": ["Philippines", "South Africa", "Peru"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dr. Marvins family featured in the movie What About Bob? really likes Bob Wiley. What does Dr. Marvins daughter Anna invite Bob to do with her?", "correct_answer": "go sailing with her and her friends", "incorrect_answers": ["go to a father-daughter dance", "go to the zoo", "go to a fair"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sport was invented by James Naismith in 1891?", "correct_answer": "basketball", "incorrect_answers": ["soccer", "ice hockey", "curling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the study of whales called?", "correct_answer": "cetology", "incorrect_answers": ["mycology", "dendrology", "balinology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The terms smiley and emoticon refer to one and the same thing.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rumpole from the fabulous British TV series Rumpole of the Bailey likes his job defending people in court and does not want to be a judge. What is Rumpoles first name?", "correct_answer": "Horace", "incorrect_answers": ["Leo", "Maurice", "Lionel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 21, the group of card counters is led by one of Bens professors. What subject does that professor teach?", "correct_answer": "Math", "incorrect_answers": ["English", "Philosophy", "Science"]}]